

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>http://localhost:4000/</id>
  <title>Eric Jones</title>
  <subtitle>A 28 year old nerd and photographer figuring out his place on this giant spinning rock that’s revolving around an even larger ball of gas.</subtitle>
  <updated>2023-11-23T00:04:18-08:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Eric Jones</name>
    <uri>http://localhost:4000/</uri>
  </author>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml"/>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"
    href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator>
  <rights> © 2023 Eric Jones </rights>
  <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon>
  <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo>


  
  <entry>
    <title>The Black Hole of Distractions and Configurations</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/black-hole-configurations-distractions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Black Hole of Distractions and Configurations" />
    <published>2023-10-08T00:00:00-07:00</published>
  
    <updated>2023-10-08T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
  
    <id>http://localhost:4000/posts/black-hole-configurations-distractions/</id>
    <content src="http://localhost:4000/posts/black-hole-configurations-distractions/" />
    <author>
      <name>Eric Jones</name>
    </author>

  
    
  

  
    <summary>
      





      I tend to find that if I’m presented with the opportunity to tinker and configure settings rather than just getting down to work, I can easily spend hours doing that and at the end of the day be annoyed that I didn’t actually doing anything productive.

I’m now at that point in my “computing life” where I value a workspace that simply works and allows me to get to what actually matters rather t...
    </summary>
  

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>Capturing Thoughts (Safely) When Driving</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/capturing-thoughts-when-driving/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Capturing Thoughts (Safely) When Driving" />
    <published>2023-10-07T00:00:00-07:00</published>
  
    <updated>2023-10-07T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
  
    <id>http://localhost:4000/posts/capturing-thoughts-when-driving/</id>
    <content src="http://localhost:4000/posts/capturing-thoughts-when-driving/" />
    <author>
      <name>Eric Jones</name>
    </author>

  
    
  

  
    <summary>
      





      When listening to podcasts while I’m driving to work, I often think of things that I want to expand on later. I find that if I don’t capture these thoughts right away then I’m trying to to juggle remembering exactly what I want to act on later while also trying to listen to the remainder of the podcast. This is a pretty poor system because I’m not fully invested in what I’m listening to and the...
    </summary>
  

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>Automating GoodLinks and My Read Later Workflow</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/automating-goodlinks-read-later-workflow/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Automating GoodLinks and My Read Later Workflow" />
    <published>2023-05-16T00:00:00-07:00</published>
  
    <updated>2023-05-16T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
  
    <id>http://localhost:4000/posts/automating-goodlinks-read-later-workflow/</id>
    <content src="http://localhost:4000/posts/automating-goodlinks-read-later-workflow/" />
    <author>
      <name>Eric Jones</name>
    </author>

  
    
  

  
    <summary>
      





      I often find articles while I’m at work that I’d like to save for reading later. On my personal devices that’s a pretty simple task - I just use the share extension within Safari to quickly send a URL to my GoodLinks account.

Understandably, I don’t really want to add any of my personal accounts to a company owned computer (let alone we can’t even install non approved apps), so I’ve resorted t...
    </summary>
  

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>AirPods Pro 2</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/airpods-pro-2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AirPods Pro 2" />
    <published>2023-04-17T00:00:00-07:00</published>
  
    <updated>2023-04-17T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
  
    <id>http://localhost:4000/posts/airpods-pro-2/</id>
    <content src="http://localhost:4000/posts/airpods-pro-2/" />
    <author>
      <name>Eric Jones</name>
    </author>

  
    
  

  
    <summary>
      





      I’ve lived with the struggle of being overly sensitive to loud noises pretty much my entire life. Recently, I decided to pick up a pair of 2nd generation AirPod Pros. I was hesitant when placing the order, wondering if these were going to be worth the money, but let me tell you… these headphones are one of the best purchases that I’ve made in a long time.

I can now walk to work on a busy weeke...
    </summary>
  

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>My Computing Journey</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/my-computing-journey/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Computing Journey" />
    <published>2023-02-05T00:00:00-08:00</published>
  
    <updated>2023-02-05T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
  
    <id>http://localhost:4000/posts/my-computing-journey/</id>
    <content src="http://localhost:4000/posts/my-computing-journey/" />
    <author>
      <name>Eric Jones</name>
    </author>

  
    
  

  
    <summary>
      





      To give a little history, the first computer that I remember using was a PC in the shape of a bread box that ran Windows XP. I would spend hours upon hours after I got out of class in high school chatting with friends, and admittedly crushes, on AOL Instant Messenger happily neglecting whatever homework that was due the following day. After using it for a number of years I was able to begin my ...
    </summary>
  

  </entry>

</feed>


